Navigating the Unity editor interface is easy.
Unity エディタ のインタフェースを操作するのは簡単です。
The core of the interface consists of five main panels.
インタフェースのコアは 5 つのメインパネルから構成されます。
The Scene View, the Hierarchy, the Game View,
シーンビュー、Hierarchy ビュー、ゲームビュー、
the Project panel and the Inspector panel.
プロジェクトパネル、およびインスペクタパネルです。
The Scene View is where you'll visually construct your game,
シーンビューはゲームを視覚的に構築する場所で、
manipulating objects in 2D and 3D.
オブジェクトを 2D および 3D で変更します。
The Game View is where you will preview your game,
ゲームビューはゲームのプレビューをする場所であり、
and this becomes active when you hit the play button,
ゲームの Play ボタンを押すと有効になり、
allowing you to play test at any time inside the editor.
これによりいつでもエディタ上でテストを行うことが出来ます。
The Hierarchy lists all objects in the scene in alphabetical order
Hierarchy ビューでは、シーンの全てのオブジェクトをアルファベット順に並べます。
and in hierarchical order in order to show parenting,
そして階層順に表示して親子関係を示し、
a way of grouping objects.
これはオブジェクトをグルーピングする方法です。
The Project panel shows all assets that you are
プロジェクトパネルは作業している、
currently working with, in one place.
全てのアセットを一箇所に表示します。
Giving you quick access to everything you are building your game with
これにより、ゲームで作成している全てのもの、
from scripts to textures, 3D models, video and audio.
すなわちスクリプト、テクスチャ、3D モデル、ビデオ、音声へのアクセスを容易にします。
The Inspector is a context sensitive panel
インスペクタはコンテキスト依存のパネルであり、
that shows the properties of what ever object,
あらゆるオブジェクト、すなわち自身で選択した
asset or setting panel you've selected.
アセットまたは設定パネルを表示します。
Click on something new and the Inspector immediately
何か新しいものをクリックすれば、
switches to show properties of that thing.
インスペクタは自動的にそのプロパティを表示します。
The play controls allow you to play test the game,
プレイ コントロールによりゲームをテスト再生や
pause and progress frame by frame for more detailed testing.
ポーズ、さらにはより詳細なテストではフレーム毎の進捗を確認出来ます。
The tools in the top left allow you to navigate the Scene View
左上のツールによりシーンビューを操作できて、
and also manipulate objects visually.
さらにオブジェクトを視覚的に変更できます。
There are also toggles to allow for switching between local and world space
さらに、ローカル空間またはワールド空間の間を切り替える
and centre or pivot point based rotation.
原点またはピボット地点をベースにした中心点を変更できます。
The Layers dropdown allows you to quickly
Layers ドロップダウンによりクイックに
show and hide layers of content in your game.
ゲームにおけるコンテンツのレイヤーの表示および非表示ができます。
The Layout dropdown allows you to switch between
Layout ドロップダウンにより
differing layouts of the Unity interface.
Unity インタフェースにおける異なるレイアウト間を切り替えることが出来ます。
In the top right of the interface are the layers and layout dropdowns.
インタフェースの右上は、 Layer および レイアウトのドロップダウンです。
This concludes the interface overview.
これでインタフェースの概要は完了です。
Continue to watch tutorials to learn more about each individual panel.
各々のパネルの詳細については、続けてチュートリアルを視聴下さい。 (翻訳:gamesonytablet)